http://www.applied-maths.com/privacy-policy-applied-maths

Applied Maths
Manage. Analyze. Discover.
Dropdown
SoftwareBioNumericsApplicationsLicensing optionsConfigure nowOther packagesBioNumerics ServerCalculation EngineServicesWorkshopsOn-site trainingData analysisScript developmentOrderDistributorsRequest a quoteGet free trialRequest license stringRequest Calculation Engine projectBuy Calculation Engine creditsSupportKnowledge BaseFAQTutorial moviesTutorialsAsk a support questionDownloadBrochuresSoftwareManualsSample dataOpen source projects
You are hereHome › Privacy policy at Applied Maths
Privacy policy at Applied Maths
Applied Maths is concerned about protecting your privacy. You are entitled to know what information we collect, and how we use it.
Cookie policy
Cookies are small text files stored on your your computer, tablet or mobile phone when you access a website on the internet. They are used to improve the online experience of almost every website, including ours. Cookies generally do not hold any information to identify an individual person, but are instead used to identify a browser on an individual machine.
Cookies set by this website:
has_js: this cookie is set by the Drupal content management system. The cookie records whether the user has javascript enabled which can help the site present information appropriately.
__utma, __umtb, __utmc, __utmv, __utmz: these cookies are created by Google Analytics. The cookies record information about the first visit to the site, the last visit to the site, the number of visits to the site, duration of site visits, and the link or search terms used to get to the site. Google Analytics is Google's free web analytics tool that helps website owners understand how their visitors engage with their website. Google Analytics collects information anonymously, and it reports website trends without identifying individual visitors.
Using www.applied-maths.com means you agree to our use of cookies. You can choose to restrict or block cookies set on this website through your browser settings at any time. For more information about how to do this, and about cookies in general, you can visit www.allaboutcookies.org.
What information we collect
Applied Maths will only collect your personal information if you filled in a form to request information, support, quotes, upgrades, evaluation licenses, or workshop participation. Applied Maths may record IP addresses only for the purposes of improving the accuracy of hit frequency statistics. Applied Maths does not use IP addresses to link to personal information.
How we collect and use your information
Your personal information is maintained and controlled by Applied Maths only and is not shared with any third party without your approval. For some countries, we may request your approval to forward your information to an accredited distributor. We will not disclose, sell or rent your personal contact information to other companies. The Applied Maths Web site has several forms that may require you to provide your name, mailing address, phone, fax number, and e-mail address. We use this contact information to send promotional material about our company and products. If you have purchased our software or expressed an interest in Applied Maths products, we may use this information to notify you of new products, updates, or other information. You may choose not to receive this additional information (see "How to unsubscribe", below).
How to unsubscribe
Applied Maths sends email messages and postal mail to announce events such as training courses and workshops, product upgrades, new product information, etc. You may choose to not receive these types of correspondence. To remove your name from e-mail or postal mail lists, please check the relevant box on the web forms, or simply send us an e-mail.
Note: Customers cannot unsubscribe from operational correspondence, such as e-mails containing License Strings and product upgrade notices.
If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please contact us.
© 2020 Applied Maths NV. All rights reserved.
Distributorship
Privacy policy
License agreement
